<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<movielist>
  <movie>
    <title>Season of The Witch</title>
    <genre>Sci-Fi</genre>
    <year>2011</year>
    <description>14th-century knights transport a suspected witch to a monastery, where monks deduce her powers could be the source of the Black Plague.</description>
    <image>season_of_the_witch_xlg</image>
  </movie>
  <movie>
    <title>The Green Hornet</title>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <year>2011</year>
    <description>Following the death of his father, Britt Reid, heir to his father's large company, teams up with his late dad's assistant Kato to become a masked crime fighting team.</description>
    <image>green_hornet_ver3_xlg</image>
  </movie>
  <movie>
    <title>The Dilemma</title>
    <genre>Comedy</genre>
    <year>2011</year>
    <description>A man discovers that his best friend's wife is having an affair.</description>
    <image>dilemma_xlg</image>
  </movie>
  <movie>
    <title>Death Race 2</title>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <year>2010</year>
    <description>Explores the origins of the first "Frankenstein" car driver, Carl "Luke" Lucas, who died in a race at the beginning of the first film.</description>
    <image>death_race_2</image>
  </movie>
  <movie>
    <title>The Company Men</title>
    <genre>Drama</genre>
    <year>2010</year>
    <description>The story centers on a year in the life of three men trying to survive a round of corporate downsizing at a major company - and how that affects them, their families, and their communities.</description>
    <image>company_men_ver2_xlg</image>
  </movie>
  <movie>
    <title>No Strings Attached</title>
    <genre>Comedy</genre>
    <year>2011</year>
    <description>A guy and girl try to keep their relationship strictly physical, but it's not long before they learn that they want something more.</description>
    <image>no_strings_attached_xlg</image>
  </movie>
  <movie>
    <title>The Way Back</title>
    <genre>Drama</genre>
    <year>2010</year>
    <description>Siberian gulag escapees walk 4000 miles overland to freedom in India.</description>
    <image>_1_Poster7</image>
  </movie>
  <movie>
    <title>The Mechanic</title>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <year>2011</year>
    <description>Follows an elite hit man as he teaches his trade to an apprentice who has a connection to one of his previous victims.</description>
    <image>mechanic_ver2_xlg</image>
  </movie>
  <movie>
    <title>The Rite</title>
    <genre>Horror</genre>
    <year>2011</year>
    <description>An American seminary student travels to Italy to take an exorcism course.</description>
    <image>rite_xlg</image>
  </movie>
  <movie>
    <title>Sanctum</title>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <year>2011</year>
    <description>An underwater cave diving team experiences a life-threatening crisis during an expedition to the unexplored and least accessible cave system in the world.</description>
    <image>sanctum_xlg</image>
  </movie>
  <movie>
    <title>The Other Woman</title>
    <genre>Drama</genre>
    <year>2009</year>
    <description>A drama that details the story of a woman's difficult relationship with her stepson.</description>
    <image>other_woman_xlg</image>
  </movie>
  <movie>
    <title>The Roommate</title>
    <genre>Thriller</genre>
    <year>2011</year>
    <description>College student Sara finds that her new roommate Rebecca has an obsession with her, which quickly turns violent.</description>
    <image>roommate_xlg</image>
  </movie>
  <movie>
    <title>Waiting For Forever</title>
    <genre>Drama</genre>
    <year>2010</year>
    <description>A Hollywood-set romantic tale of a guy who is content to live his life without a job yet with the love of his life, a young actress.</description>
    <image>waiting_for_forever_xlg</image>
  </movie>
  <movie>
    <title>Cedar Rapids</title>
    <genre>Comedy</genre>
    <year>2011</year>
    <description>Tim Lippe has no idea what he's in for when he's sent to Cedar Rapids, Iowa to represent his company at an annual insurance convention, where he soon finds himself under the "guidance" of three convention veterans.</description>
    <image>cedar_rapids_ver2_xlg</image>
  </movie>
  <movie>
    <title>Gnomeo &amp; Juliet</title>
    <genre>Family</genre>
    <year>2011</year>
    <description>The neighboring gardens of Montague and Capulet are at war, but the gnomes, Gnomeo and Juliet, are in love.</description>
    <image>gnomeo_and_juliet_xlg</image>
  </movie>
  <movie>
    <title>Just Go With It</title>
    <genre>Comedy</genre>
    <year>2011</year>
    <description>On a weekend trip to Hawaii, a plastic surgeon convinces his loyal assistant to pose as his soon-to-be-divorced wife in order to cover up a careless lie he told to his much-younger girlfriend.</description>
    <image>just_go_with_it_xlg</image>
  </movie>
  <movie>
    <title>The Eagle</title>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <year>2011</year>
    <description>In Roman-ruled Britain, a young Roman soldier endeavors to honor his father's memory by finding his lost legion's golden emblem.</description>
    <image>_31898</image>
  </movie>
  <movie>
    <title>I Am Number Four</title>
    <genre>Sci-Fi</genre>
    <year>2011</year>
    <description>Aliens and their Guardians are hiding on Earth from intergalactic bounty hunters. They can only be killed in numerical order, and Number Four is next on the list. This is his story.</description>
    <image>i_am_number_four_ver6_xlg</image>
  </movie>
  <movie>
    <title>Footloose</title>
    <genre>New Release</genre>
    <year>2011</year>
    <description>City teenager Ren MacCormack moves to a small town where rock music and dancing have been banned, and his rebellious spirit shakes up the populace.</description>
    <image>footloose_ver2_xlg</image>
  </movie>
  <movie>
    <title>Real Steel</title>
    <genre>New Release</genre>
    <year>2011</year>
    <description>Set in the near future, where robot boxing is a top sport, a struggling promoter feels he's found a champion in a discarded robot. During his hopeful rise to the top, he discovers he has an 11-year-old son who wants to know his father.</description>
    <image>real_steel_ver2_xlg</image>
  </movie>
</movielist>